<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on Reachy manual</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Reachy manual</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install your robot</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/install-your-robot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/install-your-robot/</guid><description>Install your robot Your Reachy is shipped already assembled and configured. It should be a matter of minutes before you start program it.
Before turning it on, it's always safer to check if you see anything unusual, in the unlikely event it has been damaged during transport. As an example, here is a box with a black Reachy with a single arm:
If you have a doubt, do not hesitate to send us a photo.</description></item><item><title>Connect to Your Robot</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/connect-to-your-robot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/connect-to-your-robot/</guid><description>Connect to your robot Everything is already installed 🎉 Reachy comes with a Raspberry-Pi 4 dedicated to its control. When you receive your Reachy, the board is pre-installed with all required softwares. So, you don't have to install anything on your computer.
This section is meant to:
let you know how to connect to the Raspberry-Pi, give you a bit more information on how things are actually working. First, you can find the Raspberry-Pi inside the trunk of the robot, as shown on this picture below.</description></item><item><title>Check the status of Reachy</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/check-status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/check-status/</guid><description>Check the status of Reachy Check the mechanics Once connected, the next step is to check that everything is ok. The first thing to check is that the robot is ok. You should check that the arm are in a correct position, otherwise they may turn to go back to their base position and unplug a wire.
The base position of the arm looks like this:
TODO
You should also make sure the head is in a base position, meaning looking in front of it.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2019-docs/docs/getting-started/faq/</guid><description>FAQ Can I run the software on my own computer? Yes, most of it. Our main required dependency is USB to serial communication using the serial library. Yet, you will not have access to the camera or our vision primitive that relies on specific hardware (Raspberry-Pi camera and Google Coral TPU).
Where are the installed packages on the Raspberry-Pi? All python packages can be found in $HOME/dev.
Can I have multiple instances connected to the robot at the same time?</description></item></channel></rss>